双峰
第三季第六集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛   小酸奶   吃冰棒
翻译     詹木头   一只虾
校对     小酸奶
我半小时前就请您离开了  先生
I told you to be on your way half an hour ago, sir.
时间轴     没有影子   知之
后期     8T
这里不准瞎晃
There's no loitering here.
总监     小酸奶
你叫什么名字  先生
What's your name, sir?
你叫什么  先生
道吉·琼斯
Dougie Jones.
你住在哪里  琼斯先生
And where do you live, Mr. Jones?
家
Home.
家在哪
And where is home?
不行  不能摸警徽
No-no-no-no. Don't touch the badge.
兰斯洛特
Lancelot.
兰斯洛特法院
Lancelot Court?
红色的门
Red door.
你喝酒了吗  先生
Have you been drinking, sir?
或是服用了任何药物
Any drugs or medications?
你吃了什么吗
Have you taken anything?
档案
Case file.
跟我走
Come with me.
走吧
Come on.
来了
Just a second.
道吉
Dougie?
女士  你认得这个人吗
Ma'am, do you know this man?
当然
Uh, yes, of course I do.
他是我丈夫  道吉·琼斯
He's my husband, Dougie Jones.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
他好像有点分不清方向
He seems a little disoriented.
这还算好的呢
That's on a good day.
他没有身份证件
He has no identification,
也说不出街道地址
and he wasn't able to give me the street address.
他只知道门的颜色
He only knew the house by the color of the door.
非常感谢你们
thank you, very much,
警官  谢谢你们带他回来
officers, for bringing him home.
进来吧  亲爱的
Come on, sweetheart.
咱们进屋
Let's get you in.
警徽
Badge.
对  这是我的警徽  先生
Yes, that's my badge, sir, yeah.
他对我的警徽异常迷恋  我不知道
He's got this thing for my badge, I don't know...
他就喜欢...
He likes...
谢谢  谢谢你了  警官
Thank you. Thank you, officer.
快进来
Come on in.
女士
Uh, ma'am?
这有个信封是你们的
There's an envelope here for you.
再次感谢
Thank you again.
晚安
Good night.
晚安  女士
Good night, ma'am.
道吉  对不起  我忘了你没车
Dougie, I'm sorry, I forgot, your car.
你的车呢
Where is your car?
你吃东西了吗
Have you eaten?
来  我给你做个三明治
Come on. I'm gonna fix you a sandwich.
明天午休时  我要带你去见本医生
Tomorrow lunchtime, I'm taking you to see Dr. Ben.
得让他好好看看你
He needs to take a good look at you.
看看你
Look at you.
这些是什么
And what are these?
档案
Case files.
还有这个
And this one...
这上面什么都没写
...there's nothing written on it.
好吧  道吉
Okay, Dougie,
你得上楼
you need to go upstairs
去跟桑尼·吉姆说晚安
and say good night to Sonny Jim.
他一直醒着在等你
He's been waiting up for you.
等你
Up for you.
上楼去跟桑尼·吉姆说晚安
Go upstairs and say good night to Sonny Jim.
上楼
Upstairs!
道吉
Dougie.
我已经刷过牙了
I already brushed my teeth.
我能不关牛仔灯吗
Can I leave my cowboy light on?
你能等我睡着了再走吗
Will you stay with me until I fall asleep?
睡着
Asleep.
爸爸
Dad.
道吉
Dougie!
马上给我下来
Get down here right now!
快点
Right now!
妈  他要陪我的
Mom! He was gonna stay with me!
今晚不行
Not tonight, he isn't.
妈妈一会就上去  宝贝
Mommy will be up soon, honey.
赶紧下来  快点
Get down here, right now!
你麻烦大了  先生
You are in the doghouse, mister.
你本该打给他们
You were supposed to call them
约好时间把钱给他们
and set up a time to pay them off,
结果你看看  这东西出现了
and look, this shows up!
你有什么解释吗
Do you have an explanation for this?
杰德
Jade.
Jade?
她叫杰德是吧
So that's her name, is it?
杰德载了我两程
Jade give two rides.
我猜也是
I'll bet she did.
你承认你认识她
And you admit you know her.
看看你俩  那样搂在一起
Look at you two, holding each other like that.
你要接吗
Are you gonna answer that?
也许是杰德打来的呢
Maybe it's Jade calling!
杰德
Jade.
我的天  道吉
Oh, my God, Dougie.
这事没完
We are not done with this.
喂
Hello?
道格·琼斯
Doug Jones.
你是哪位
Who is this?
道格...琼斯
Doug...Jones.
他不舒服
He's indisposed.
你收到我们的信封了吗
Did you get our envelope?
是的我收到了  真是谢谢你了
Yes, I did, thank you very much.
现在你听我说
Now, you listen to me.
他欠你多少钱
How much does he owe you?
他跟你说了吗
Did he tell you?
他没跟我说过
No, he didn't tell me.
我也是现在才知道这事的
I'm just finding out about all this right now.
五万美元
Fifty thousand.
他怎样凑那么多钱出来
A--and how's he supposed to get that?
谁会有那么多钱
Who can get that kind of money?
如果他没有这么多钱呢
And what if he doesn't have it?
你打算怎么做  打断他的腿吗
What are you gonna do then? Break his legs?
想想吧  凑这钱已经够难了
Think about it; it's hard enough to get that kind of money,
你打断他的腿了就更加不可能凑到了
let alone with broken legs.
五万美元  到期
Fifty thousand dollars, past due.
我们明天打电话去他办公室的时候
It'd be real smart for Mr. Jones
他最好是凑足了钱
to have that on him tomorrow when we call his office.
别  别  不要  不要
No, no, no, no.
你休想去他的办公室搞事
Don't you dare go to his office.
我会亲自跟你谈谈
I'll talk to you myself.
公园里面  靠近商场那个
In the park, at the corner of Guinevere and Merlin
吉尼维尔和梅林的角落
by the mall.
到时我会拿着红色的手提包
I'll be the one carrying the red purse.
红色手提包
Red purse.
时间呢
When?
明天中午十二点半
Noon-thirty tomorrow.
你看看你干的好事  道吉
What a mess you've made of our lives, Dougie.
我该拿你怎么办好
Now, what am I gonna do with you?
我本来打算在午饭时间
I was gonna take you to see Dr. Ben tomorrow
带你去看本医生的
during your lunch hour.
但我要在十二点半跟你朋友见面
And now I have to meet your friends at 12:30.
我...你的车呢  还有你钱包去哪了
I--w-where's your car? And your wallet?
你的钱包跟身份证都跑哪去了
What happened to your wallet and your identification?
如果那些是工作文件  你最好现在就开始干活
And if that's work, you better get started right away.
我们可不想你丢了工作  道吉
The last thing we need is you losing your job, Dougie.
好了  现在
Okay, now,
我要上楼跟桑尼·吉姆说晚安
I'm gonna go upstairs and say good night to Sonny Jim.
明天是个重要的日子
Tomorrow's a big day.
重要的日子
Big day.
-道吉  -重要的日子
- Oh, Dougie... - Big day.
是的  亲爱的
Yes, sweetheart.
幸运7号保险公司
你
必须
醒过来
快醒过来
别死
别死啊
盗窃类索赔表
幸运7号保险公司
非放弃条款契约
安东尼·辛克莱
幸运7号保险公司
克拉克县
调查人员  卢米斯警官和斯托克顿警官
祝你今晚愉快  戈登
You have a super night too, Gordon.
我不知道我什么时候才能回家
I don't know when I'm gonna get home.
谢谢  艾伯特
Thank you, Albert.
我要提醒你
And let me remind you
你今晚执行的任务
that this work you are doing tonight
超级无敌重要
is very, very important.
我一喝这个就想到你
And I will be thinking of you as I drink this...
给你
Here you go.
谢谢  宝贝
Thank you, sweetheart.
波尔多精品白兰地
...fine Bordeaux.
是的  我喜欢这小镇的夜晚
Yes, I love a night on the town
现1度还下着雨
when it's 34 degrees and raining.
吉恩·凯利  你这混蛋
Fuck Gene Kelly, you motherfucker!
玛·安酒吧
戴安
Diane.
你好  艾伯特
Hello, Albert.
华盛顿
操
Ah, shit.
这真是
That is... whoo!
没错  很爽吧
That's right, small time.
你可以
You can, uh,
你可以在玛丽·安那里把剩下的都拿了
you can pick the rest of it up at Mary Ann's.
你怎么知道那名字
How'd you know that name?
你知道那地方吗
You know the area?
操
Shit.
这玩意劲真大
Oh, tha--this stuff kicks.
你有研究过你的手吗
Have you ever studied your hand?
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
过去的几个星期我一直待在这里
I've been all around here last couple of weeks.
我
I, uh...
我喜欢这里
I like it.
我们可以  我们可以把那东西
We can-- we can move the sparkle
直接从加拿大拿过来
right down from Canada.
是的
Yeah.
我的肝有点问题
I got a problem with my liver.
这些小城镇的人
These fucking little towns,
很容易搞定的  不是吗
they're a pushover, right?
执法的人都是浑浑噩噩的
Law enforcement's asleep at the wheel.
这里的警长好像90岁来着
Fuckin' sheriff here is like 90 years old or something.
你看过《国王与我》这部电影吗
Did you ever the see the movie The King and I?
什么
What?
我喜欢那电影
I said I like it.
你怎么看
What do you think?
你
You, uh,
你把局面控制住了吗
you got this under control?
控制住了
Yeah.
最好是这样
You better have.
还有一个问题
There's--there's one problem.
我还不了解你
I don't know you yet.
我会盯着你的  小子
I'm gonna be watching you, kid.
盯着你
I'm watching you.
明白了吗
Got that?
是
Yeah.
我明白了
I got it.
别叫我"小子"
Don't call me "kid."
记住这个
Just-- just remember this,
小子...
kid...
我会看着你脑袋开花
...I will saw your head open
然后吃掉你的脑花
and eat your brains
如果你把事办砸了
if you fuck me over.
走着瞧
You can count on that.
这是你
This is you.
这是我
This is me.
正  我赢
Heads, I win.
反  你输
Tails, you lose.
"小子"
"Kid."
去你妈的
Fuck you, man!
冷静  冷静
Come on. Come on.
早上好  比尔
Morning, Bill.
卡尔
Hey, Carl!
什么事
Yeah?
能载我去趟城里吗
Can I get a ride with you into town?
我得去邮局取琳达的邮件
I-I gotta pick up Linda's mail at the P.O.
没问题  米基
Sure, Mickey.
比尔
Bill.
早上景色真不错  不是吗
Beautiful morning, huh?
你
You, uh,
你每天都这个时候进城 不是吗
you go into town about this time every day, don't you?
差不多吧
Damn near.
为什么
How come?
我可以离开这个拖车公园
Gets me out of this trailer park.
我这个年纪已经没有什么念想了  米基
Not much I got to look forward to at my age, Mickey,
每天就是等死
except the hammer slamming down.
别这么说  卡尔
Don't say that, Carl.
你还有很长的路要走呢
You know, you got a lot of tread left.
琳达怎么样了
How's Linda?
好多了
She's doing a lot better.
终于要政府部门送来了
Got the government agencies to finally get
一台电动轮椅
one of them electric wheelchairs.
该死的战争
Fuckin' war.
政府在照顾你  是吗
So the government's taking care of you, huh?
没多大帮助
Not hardly.
我们花了六个月才要到这个轮椅
Took us about six months to get this wheelchair for her.
该死的政府
Fuckin' government.
想抽烟吗
Want a smoke?
想
Yeah.
想抽  但我已经戒烟了
Yeah, but I quit.
戒烟
Quit?
是的
Yeah.
大约一年前就戒了
Quit about a year ago.
我抽了75年的烟了
I've been smoking for 75 years,
每天都抽
every fucking day.
有人路过那间商店时  我心想
So when I pass that shop, I say,
"不知他们有没有写了我名字的杯子蛋糕"
"Oh, I wonder if they have a cupcake with my name on it."
我进店一看  他们果然有
And when I go in, sure enough, they have it.
很神奇
It's magic.
我路过双R餐厅时  心想
And when I pass by the Double R, I say,
"不知他们有没有
"Hm, I wonder if they have
写了我名字的樱桃派"
a slice of cherry pie with my name on it."
我一进店  你们果真也有
And when I come in, sure enough, you have it.
今天你们有两块
Today you had two pieces of pie
写了我名字的派  两块我都要了
with my name on it, each one.
米里亚姆  我发现
Well, Miriam, it turns out
你是我们店有史以来的最佳买派的顾客
you're one of our best pie customers ever.
因为诺玛做的派最好吃
Because Norma makes the best pies.
那是当然
She sure does.
对了  我能买两杯咖啡带走吗
Oh, hey, can I get two cups of coffee to go?
我的那杯要低咖啡因的
One decaf for me and one regular
一杯常规的给我妈  她超爱双R餐厅的咖啡
for one of the moms who loves Double R coffee?
-马上来  -太好了
- Coming right up. - Excellent.
学校怎么样了  米里亚姆
How is school, Miriam?
今年学校里的孩子都很可爱
Oh, the kids this year are so cute.
好了  给你
Okay, here you go.
不用找了  给你们俩的小费
Keep the change. The tip is for you all.
谢谢你  米里亚姆
Oh, thank you, Miriam.
-谢谢你  米里亚姆  -再见
- Thank you, Miriam. - Bye.
她没这么阔气能给这么多小费
She can't afford to leave a tip like that.
我知道  可怜的人儿
I know. Poor thing.
但她真的很喜欢我们的派
But she just loves our pies.
知道吗  下次  咱们请她吃
You know what? Next time, let's treat her.
行啊  太好了  好主意
Oh, yeah, great. Great idea.
白痴耍魔术的
Stupid magic motherfucker.
"小子"
Ha, yeah, "kid"?
我要给你们看看小子的本事
I'll show you fucking kid.
抓住你了
Got ya.
什么玩意
What the fuck?
去他妈的
Fuck this.
全路禁止通行
不
No!
Oh, no.
不
No.
天啊
Oh, God.
我都说了
Hey! Hey, I told you
不要挡我的路
to get out of the fucking way!
不
No.
天啊
God.
格雷戈
Greg!
找到车牌了
I found the plate.
一一九
One-one-nine!
D U G E
David, union, George, Edward,
L V
Lincoln, victor.
写下来了吗
Copy?
写好了
Got it.
道吉
Dougie?
Dougie.
道吉
快别闹了
Quit clowning around.
道吉
Dougie--
Dougie.
道吉
快过来
Come on.
琼斯
Jones!
道吉
Dougie!
到我办公室来
In my office!
快点
Now!
这都是些
What the hell
什么乱七八糟的简笔画
are all these childish scribbles?
这我怎么能看得明白
H-how am I gonna make any sense out of this?
看...
Make...
...明白
...sense of it.
我觉得你真该
I'm thinking you may need
去找专业的医生帮帮你了  道吉
some good professional help, Dougie.
帮帮道吉
Help Dougie.
最强硬汉
布什内尔·拳击新星·穆林斯
道吉
Dougie.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我希望你能不要再告诉别人
I want you to keep this information to yourself.
这事挺闹心的
This is disturbing.
也不只是闹心了
To say the least.
这些就交给我吧
I'll take it from here.
但我可能还会找你帮忙
But I may need your help again.
你可是又给我添了不少要办的事情啊
You've certainly given me a lot to think about.
办事情
Think about.
道吉
Dougie?
你真是...  挺有趣的
You're an-- an interesting fellow.
你是琼斯吗
You Jones?
是我  我们就直说了吧
Yes. Now let's get to it.
给我解释一下道吉到底干了什么
Explain to me exactly what Dougie did
才欠了你们的钱
to make him owe you money.
他借的
He borrowed it.
什么叫"他借的"
What do you mean, "He borrowed it"?
他赌了一场橄榄球赛
He took points on a football game.
后来胃口大了  加了双倍
He got greedy, he doubled down.
结果最后没赢
It didn't work out for him.
赔了两万  还有利息
Out 20 grand he was, plus interest.
这已经是三周前的事了
Now, that was three weeks ago.
利息还在加呢
Meter's still running.
已经涨到五万二了
It's up to 52.
先让我来捋一捋  有这么一场球赛
So let me get this straight. People were playing games.
他打了个赌输了两万
He made a bet where he lost $20,000.
然后你们想让他给五万二
But you want him to pay you back $52,000?
没错  是这样的
Very good. That's correct.
好吧  那你们听清楚了
Okay, so you get this straight.
我的丈夫有份工作  结了婚
My husband has a job; he has a wife;
还有个孩子  他挣的钱根本
he has a child; he does not make enough money
拿不出五万二  不管是干什么
to pay back $52,000 for anything.
我们算不上有钱
We are not wealthy people.
开的都是廉价的破车
We drive cheap, terrible cars.
我们就是些平民百姓
We are the 99 percenters.
我们已经被欺负的够多了
And we are shit on enough.
但我们绝对忍不了再听任
And we are certainly not gonna be shit on
你们这种人摆布
by the likes of you.
不过  女士...
Nevertheless, lady...
所以我们就这么办了
So here's what we're gonna do.
在我不知情的情况下  我丈夫找你们
Without my knowledge, my husband came to you
借了两万
for a loan of $20,000.
你们也很好心的借给他了
You were nice enough to give it to him.
但他决不该像这个样子赌钱
But he should never have been gambling like that.
我会把钱还给你们的
I'm gonna pay you back.
不过在银行里  我们就只挣
Now, at my bank, where we make
不到百分之一的利息
less than one percent interest
原本存的钱也不多
on what little money we have,
你借钱能要到百分之二十五的利息
people would be turning cartwheels
就该高兴到翻跟头了
just to get 25 percent interest on any loan,
这些就是我现在很大方的
and that is what I'm generously
准备给你们的数
gonna give to you right now,
两万五千块
$25,000.
这些就是我第一次  也是最后一次
That is my first, last,
会给你们的全部的钱  仅此一次
and only offer to you.
这究竟是个什么世道
What kind of world are we living in
才会有你们这种人
where people can behave like this?
竟能这个样子对别人
Treat other people this way
毫无恻隐之情
without any compassion
也不体谅他人的痛苦
or feeling for their suffering?
我们生存在一个无比黑暗的年代
We are living in a dark, dark age,
而你们
and you
也是问题根源的一部分
are part of the problem.
我建议你们好好看看你们自己
Now, I suggest you take a good, long look at yourselves
因为我再也不想看到你们了
because I never want to see either of you again.
这小妞真狠
Tough dame.
真狠
Tough.
什么叫他不在车里  三具尸体
What do you mean he wasn't in the car? Three bodies?
不
Oh, no.
操
Fuck!
奈兹·珀斯制造
你干什么
The hell?
上女厕所  查德
Use the ladies' room, Chad.
你在干什么
The hell are you doing?
拜托  查德
Please, Chad,
去别的隔间上厕所
use another restroom.
你和警长说过了吗
Clear this with the sheriff?
你不说的话我说
I'll tell him if you don't.
去说吧  查德
Yeah, you do that, Chad.
写报告一点都没意思  伙计们
Filling out paperwork's no fun, fellows.
我知道  但是总得写
I know that, but, uh, gotta be done.
等你做完...这堆破事
And when you finish... That motherfucking piece of shit.
我要你处理...
...I want you to handle that...
惊喜吧  惊喜吧
Well, surprise, surprise!
没有修好
It's not fixed!
怎么了  多丽丝
What's that, Doris?
爸爸的车
Dad's car.
今天早上他要开
This morning he went to drive,
根本开不出车道  弗兰克
couldn't even get it out of the driveway, Frank!
只会一晃一晃
It just lurched and lurched.
他应该没有放手刹吧
Sounds like he left the emergency brake on.
你是说我爸爸不知道怎么开车吗
Are you telling me my father doesn't know how to drive a car?
你是想说这个吗
Is that what you're telling me?
你别想
Don't you dare,
你别想把这开不了的破车
don't you dare try to blame my father
怪到我爸爸头上
for that car not running right!
如果能让你好受点
We'll get it looked at again
我们就再找人来看看
if it'll make you feel better.
好受点  好受点
Feel better? Feel better?
为什么  你为什么老和我对着干  弗兰克
Why, why are you always against me, Frank?
去我办公室吧
Let's go to my office.
他们修得太差了
They did a lousy job fixing that car.
他们得修好
They have to make it right,
不然我们就不付钱
or we're not paying them until they do!
换我可不会受她这种鸟气
I sure wouldn't take that kind of shit off her.
怎么了
What?
你根本不知道你自己在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
是吗  怎么说
Oh, yeah? How's that?
算了
Forget it.
怎么了
What's the matter?
这是个自由的世界
It's a free world.
我能表达我的观点
I can voice my opinion.
你当然可以
Oh, you sure can.
哥们儿
Oh, brother.
她以前不是这样的
She didn't use to be like this.
你不知道他们儿子自杀了吗
You didn't know that their son committed suicide?
我听说过
Yeah, I heard something about that.
他受不了成为士兵
He couldn't take being a soldier.
警局  有什么紧急情况
Sheriff's Department. What's your emergency?
你在哪里
Where's your location?
你电话多少
What's your telephone number?
*跪到地上*
*Hit the ground*
*院子里*
*The yard*
*我发现了什么*
*I found something*
*我能尝到你嘴巴的味道*
*I could taste your mouth*
*关上门*
*Shut the door*
*沐浴着阳光*
*Now in the sun tanning*
*你那么*
*You were so*
*就这么*
*Just*
*看向天空*
*Looking across the sky*
*记不清*
*Can't remember*
*我记不起来*
*I can't recall no*
*我什么都*
*I can't remember*
*记不起来*
*Anything at all*
*让我们奔跑*
*Let's run under*
*在夜里诅咒我自己*
*Cursing myself at night*
*七点慢点*
*Slow it was seven*
*我希望整晚*
*I wish it was*
*都是七点*
*Seven all night*
*告诉我何时*
*Tell me when*
*告诉我何时会结束*
*Tell me when is this over*
*吞噬你*
*Chewed you out*
*吞噬我*
*Chew me out*
*我犯傻*
*When I'm stupid*
*我不想让*
*I don't wanna*
*所有人无奈*
*Everyone else pales*
*派来猫头鹰*
*Send in the owl*
*告诉我我不是孩子*
*Tell me I'm not a child*
*你的召唤*
*You summon*
*忘记*
*Forget about*
*所有人*
*Everyone else*
*坠落*
*Fall away somehow*